I can't believe my maid-of-honor dress
is gonna be on Google Earth.
(Howard:)So we have the where
and the when...
(Howard:)...but we still need to figure out
who's gonna do the ceremony.
(Penny:)Anyone can go online
and get ordained as a minister.
I know a piercing parlor
where they'll marry you...
(Penny:)...and stick a wedding ring
through any body part you want.
Right, well, who's it gonna be?
(Sheldon:)I'll do it, provided I can perform
the ceremony in Klingon.
(Cosmonaut(in Russian):)No.
(Sheldon:)What do you see in her?
(Howard:)Leaking? what's leaking?
(Dimitri:)Fuel. Shh.
(Howard:)MAN
(Howard:)There's fuel leaking
and we're still gonna go?
(Mike:)Don't lose your Froot Loops,
Froot Loops.
(Dimitri:)This happens a lot.